The ultimate sacrifice deserves the highest honor.
The Last Full Measure is a drama, action, war film directed by Todd Robinson.
The incredible true story of Vietnam War hero William H.
Pitsenbarger, a U.S.
Air Force Pararescuemen medic who personally saved over sixty men.
Thirty-two years later, Pentagon staffer Scott Huffman investigates a Congressional Medal of Honor request for Pitsenbarger and uncovers a high-level
conspiracy behind the decades-long denial of the medal, prompting Huffman to put his own career on the line to seek justice for the fallen airman.
Scott Huffman, played by Sebastian Stan.
Frank Pitsenbarger, played by Christopher Plummer.
Tulley, played by William Hurt.
Ray Mott, played by Ed Harris.
Young Ray Mott, played by Zach Roerig.
Takoda, played by Samuel L. Jackson.
The Last Full Measure is a 2019 American war drama film
written and directed by Todd Robinson.
It follows the efforts of fictional Pentagon staffer Scott Huffman and many
veterans to see the Medal of Honor awarded to William H.
Pitsenbarger, a United States Air Force Pararescueman who flew in helicopter rescue
missions during the Vietnam War to aid downed soldiers and pilots.
Based on true events, the film stars Sebastian Stan,
Christopher Plummer, William Hurt, Ed Harris, Samuel L.
Jackson, Jeremy Irvine, and Peter Fonda.
It was the final film appearance of Fonda, who died before the film’s release; and Plummer's final on screen
appearance before his death in 2021, though it had filmed prior to Knives Out, which was released before it.
Production began in the United States in March 2017, and it
premiered in October 2019 in Westhampton Beach, New York.
It was released in the U.S.
by Roadside Attractions on January 24, 2020, and grossed
$3 million against a $20 million budget.
Its title is from Abraham Lincoln's Gettysburg Address, where Lincoln honored the
fallen, saying that they "gave the last full measure of devotion."
The film explores themes of vietnam war, affectation,
based on true story, grim, inspirational.
The tone is emotional.